A Finding Aid to the Frances Wolfson Art Gallery Records, 1973-1994, in the Archives of American Art AAA.franwola
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1977-1992, undated; Series 4; 4.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-5
  - The South Florida Collective 1 (Sept 5-Oct 31, 1991), 1985-1992 (Box 4, Folder 27-34)
    Mary Lee Adler-Ataie, Shahreyar Ataie, Maria Brito, Carol Brown, Pablo Cano, Michael L. Carlebach, Rosemarie Chiarlone, Maggie Davis, Demi [Rodriguez], Russell Frehling, Fernando Garcia, Marilyn Gottlieb-Roberts, Joe Nicastri, Elena Presser, Charles Recher, Arturo Rodriguez, Lydia Rubio, Ward Shelley, Cesar Trasobares, and Purvis Young (includes 18 artist files for each artist, except Demi and Charles Recher, containing primarily resumés, clippings, and miscellaneous exhibition announcements)
  - Personal Prophecies (Sept 10-Oct 10, 1991), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 35-40)
    Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz, Sylvia Gruner, and Eugenia Vargas-Daniels (includes a typescript about Gruner)
  - Abstractions (Sept 12-Oct 17, 1991) (Box 4, Folder 41-43)
    Juan Carlos Garcia-Lavin, Jose Iraola, and Luis Marin (includes a typescript for the catalog Without, Against and With the Figure by Juan Espinosa Almodovar)
  - Le Boom Belge! (The Belgian Boom) (Oct 24-Nov 27, 1991), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
    Guillaume Bijl, Leo Copers, Wim Delvoye, Jan Fabre, Marie Jo Lafontaine, and Marc Maet
  - Porkopolis (Oct 29-Dec 10, 1991), 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
    Sue Coe (includes a typescript Slaughterhouse Journal by Coe and a brochure Porkopolis)
  - Memorial/Remembrance (Nov 7-Dec 13, 1991) (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    Nat Dean
  - DiAna's Hair Ego: AIDS Info Up Front (Nov 28 and Nov 30, 1991), 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Video, Ellen Spiro
  - Art Against AIDS III (Dec 7, 1991) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Evolving Fragments (Dec 12, 1991-Feb 28, 1992), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Alberto Torre de Alba
  - Blues, Bop & Beyond (Jan 30-Mar 19, 1992), 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 13-16)
    David D. Spitzer (includes 4 photographs of jazz musicians Miles Davis, Bobby McFerrin, and Sonny Rollins, and 2 contact sheets of the gallery opening)
  - Unbeknownst (Feb 13-Mar 26, 1992), 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17-19)
    Gary Moore and Deryl Mackie
  - Kinetic Sculpture - Art That Moves (Apr 1-May 15, 1992), 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Robert Mark Packer
  - Annual Juried Student Exhibition (Apr 9-30, 1992) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pedro Mendez Mercado: In His Time (1902-1990) (Apr 23-May 29, 1992), 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 22-34)
    (includes a biographical sketch)
  - Painting, Drawings, Video (May 7-28, 1992) (Box 5, Folder 35-37)
    Tom Downs and Rebecca Howland, Fellows of National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts (NFAA), Career Advancement of Visual Artists Program (CAVA) (includes an essay about Downs); see also May 2-18, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Printed Material, 1974-1994; Series 5; 5 Folders Box 5
  This series consists of miscellaneous clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs, and a copy of the booklet Directory of Speakers, Artists, and Research Areas for the Women's Caucus for Art National.
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs from Other Galleries, 1974-1994 (Box 5, Folder 39-41)
    (arranged chronologically including: Beckman, William, 1986; Cardenas, Juan, 1985; Castles, John, 1981; Castoro, Rosemarie, 1987; Clemente, Francesco, 1985; Cruz-Azaceta, Luis, 1988; Csernus, Tibor, 1985; Curtis, Brian, 1989; Denes, Agnes, 1980; de Roiter, Sara Modiano, 1981; Duque, Alberto Uribe, 1981; Estopinan, Roberto, 1988; Galletti, Lia, 1988; Garcez, Paulo Gomes, 1988; Gomez, Victor, 1988; Gonzalez, Beatriz, 1978; Merlino, Silvio, 1987; Morales, Armando, 1986; Neblett, Alexandra, 1988; Page, Judith, 1986; Pinto, Jody, 1987; Rojas, Miguel Angel, 1981; Roszak, Sara, 1982; Salcedo, Bernardo, 1981; Seliger, Charles, 1974-1982; Solow, Peter, 1989; Valerio, James, undated; Zaborov, Boris, 1985)
  - Directory of Speakers, Artists, and Research Areas for the Women's Caucus for Art National, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Color Transparencies of Artwork, 1983-1990; Series 6; 10 Items Box 5
  Ten color transparencies of artwork by Marcia Grostein, Jorge Pardo, Francisca Sutil, Jorge Tacla, Patricia Wahl, and P. Way.
  - Color Transparencies, 1983-1990 (Box 5, Folder 43)